{"problemsArray": [
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({4x-6}/{9}\u003d{1}/{7}\\)", "answer": "51/28", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({4x-6}/{9}*9\u003d{1}/{7}*9\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(4x-6\u003d{9}/{7}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(4x \u003d{9}/{7}+6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(4x \u003d{9}/{7}+{42}/{7}\\)\n\\(4x \u003d{51}/{7}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{51}/{28}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-2x-7}/{6}\u003d{6}/{7}\\)", "answer": "-85/14", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-2x-7}/{6}*6\u003d{6}/{7}*6\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-2x-7\u003d{36}/{7}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-2x \u003d{36}/{7}+7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-2x \u003d{36}/{7}+{49}/{7}\\)\n\\(-2x \u003d{85}/{7}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{85}/{-14}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({8x+8}/{7}\u003d{7}/{6}\\)", "answer": "1/48", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({8x+8}/{7}*7\u003d{7}/{6}*7\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(8x+8\u003d{49}/{6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(8x \u003d{49}/{6}-8\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(8x \u003d{49}/{6}+{-48}/{6}\\)\n\\(8x \u003d{1}/{6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{1}/{48}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({8x-10}/{-7}\u003d{5}/{-3}\\)", "answer": "65/24", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({8x-10}/{-7}*-7\u003d{5}/{-3}*-7\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(8x-10\u003d{-35}/{-3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(8x \u003d{-35}/{-3}+10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(8x \u003d{-35}/{-3}+{-30}/{-3}\\)\n\\(8x \u003d{-65}/{-3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-65}/{-24}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-4x-9}/{-3}\u003d{10}/{-10}\\)", "answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-4x-9}/{-3}*-3\u003d{10}/{-10}*-3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-4x-9\u003d{-30}/{-10}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-4x \u003d{-30}/{-10}+9\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-4x \u003d{-30}/{-10}+{-90}/{-10}\\)\n\\(-4x \u003d{-120}/{-10}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-120}/{40}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({5x+7}/{8}\u003d{9}/{8}\\)", "answer": "2/5", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({5x+7}/{8}*8\u003d{9}/{8}*8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(5x+7\u003d{72}/{8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(5x \u003d{72}/{8}-7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(5x \u003d{72}/{8}+{-56}/{8}\\)\n\\(5x \u003d{16}/{8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{16}/{40}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-6x-3}/{4}\u003d{-8}/{6}\\)", "answer": "7/18", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-6x-3}/{4}*4\u003d{-8}/{6}*4\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-6x-3\u003d{-32}/{6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-6x \u003d{-32}/{6}+3\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-6x \u003d{-32}/{6}+{18}/{6}\\)\n\\(-6x \u003d{-14}/{6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-14}/{-36}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-8x+7}/{-3}\u003d{3}/{4}\\)", "answer": "37/32", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-8x+7}/{-3}*-3\u003d{3}/{4}*-3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-8x+7\u003d{-9}/{4}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-8x \u003d{-9}/{4}-7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-8x \u003d{-9}/{4}+{-28}/{4}\\)\n\\(-8x \u003d{-37}/{4}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-37}/{-32}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-7x-1}/{1}\u003d{-4}/{3}\\)", "answer": "1/21", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-7x-1}/{1}*1\u003d{-4}/{3}*1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-7x-1\u003d{-4}/{3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-7x \u003d{-4}/{3}+1\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-7x \u003d{-4}/{3}+{3}/{3}\\)\n\\(-7x \u003d{-1}/{3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-1}/{-21}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-7x-7}/{-3}\u003d{4}/{-2}\\)", "answer": "-13/7", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-7x-7}/{-3}*-3\u003d{4}/{-2}*-3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-7x-7\u003d{-12}/{-2}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-7x \u003d{-12}/{-2}+7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-7x \u003d{-12}/{-2}+{-14}/{-2}\\)\n\\(-7x \u003d{-26}/{-2}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-26}/{14}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({2x+5}/{-10}\u003d{-7}/{2}\\)", "answer": "15", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({2x+5}/{-10}*-10\u003d{-7}/{2}*-10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(2x+5\u003d{70}/{2}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(2x \u003d{70}/{2}-5\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(2x \u003d{70}/{2}+{-10}/{2}\\)\n\\(2x \u003d{60}/{2}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{60}/{4}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({3x-2}/{-10}\u003d{-9}/{-1}\\)", "answer": "-88/3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({3x-2}/{-10}*-10\u003d{-9}/{-1}*-10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(3x-2\u003d{90}/{-1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(3x \u003d{90}/{-1}+2\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(3x \u003d{90}/{-1}+{-2}/{-1}\\)\n\\(3x \u003d{88}/{-1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{88}/{-3}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({5x+1}/{-6}\u003d{6}/{-8}\\)", "answer": "7/10", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({5x+1}/{-6}*-6\u003d{6}/{-8}*-6\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(5x+1\u003d{-36}/{-8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(5x \u003d{-36}/{-8}-1\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(5x \u003d{-36}/{-8}+{8}/{-8}\\)\n\\(5x \u003d{-28}/{-8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-28}/{-40}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({3x+2}/{3}\u003d{2}/{8}\\)", "answer": "-5/12", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({3x+2}/{3}*3\u003d{2}/{8}*3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(3x+2\u003d{6}/{8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(3x \u003d{6}/{8}-2\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(3x \u003d{6}/{8}+{-16}/{8}\\)\n\\(3x \u003d{-10}/{8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-10}/{24}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-7x-10}/{-8}\u003d{-1}/{4}\\)", "answer": "-12/7", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-7x-10}/{-8}*-8\u003d{-1}/{4}*-8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-7x-10\u003d{8}/{4}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-7x \u003d{8}/{4}+10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-7x \u003d{8}/{4}+{40}/{4}\\)\n\\(-7x \u003d{48}/{4}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{48}/{-28}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-8x-1}/{10}\u003d{4}/{3}\\)", "answer": "-43/24", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-8x-1}/{10}*10\u003d{4}/{3}*10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-8x-1\u003d{40}/{3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-8x \u003d{40}/{3}+1\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-8x \u003d{40}/{3}+{3}/{3}\\)\n\\(-8x \u003d{43}/{3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{43}/{-24}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({8x+1}/{-4}\u003d{8}/{-3}\\)", "answer": "29/24", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({8x+1}/{-4}*-4\u003d{8}/{-3}*-4\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(8x+1\u003d{-32}/{-3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(8x \u003d{-32}/{-3}-1\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(8x \u003d{-32}/{-3}+{3}/{-3}\\)\n\\(8x \u003d{-29}/{-3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-29}/{-24}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-10x+7}/{-6}\u003d{-8}/{8}\\)", "answer": "1/10", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-10x+7}/{-6}*-6\u003d{-8}/{8}*-6\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-10x+7\u003d{48}/{8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-10x \u003d{48}/{8}-7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-10x \u003d{48}/{8}+{-56}/{8}\\)\n\\(-10x \u003d{-8}/{8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-8}/{-80}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({9x+8}/{1}\u003d{3}/{2}\\)", "answer": "-13/18", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({9x+8}/{1}*1\u003d{3}/{2}*1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(9x+8\u003d{3}/{2}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(9x \u003d{3}/{2}-8\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(9x \u003d{3}/{2}+{-16}/{2}\\)\n\\(9x \u003d{-13}/{2}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-13}/{18}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-9x-10}/{-8}\u003d{-8}/{6}\\)", "answer": "-62/27", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-9x-10}/{-8}*-8\u003d{-8}/{6}*-8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-9x-10\u003d{64}/{6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-9x \u003d{64}/{6}+10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-9x \u003d{64}/{6}+{60}/{6}\\)\n\\(-9x \u003d{124}/{6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{124}/{-54}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({7x+6}/{8}\u003d{6}/{-1}\\)", "answer": "-54/7", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({7x+6}/{8}*8\u003d{6}/{-1}*8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(7x+6\u003d{48}/{-1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(7x \u003d{48}/{-1}-6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(7x \u003d{48}/{-1}+{6}/{-1}\\)\n\\(7x \u003d{54}/{-1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{54}/{-7}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-7x+3}/{-8}\u003d{-10}/{-5}\\)", "answer": "19/7", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-7x+3}/{-8}*-8\u003d{-10}/{-5}*-8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-7x+3\u003d{80}/{-5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-7x \u003d{80}/{-5}-3\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-7x \u003d{80}/{-5}+{15}/{-5}\\)\n\\(-7x \u003d{95}/{-5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{95}/{35}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({8x+10}/{1}\u003d{5}/{-5}\\)", "answer": "-11/8", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({8x+10}/{1}*1\u003d{5}/{-5}*1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(8x+10\u003d{5}/{-5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(8x \u003d{5}/{-5}-10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(8x \u003d{5}/{-5}+{50}/{-5}\\)\n\\(8x \u003d{55}/{-5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{55}/{-40}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({8x+7}/{5}\u003d{-4}/{5}\\)", "answer": "-11/8", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({8x+7}/{5}*5\u003d{-4}/{5}*5\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(8x+7\u003d{-20}/{5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(8x \u003d{-20}/{5}-7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(8x \u003d{-20}/{5}+{-35}/{5}\\)\n\\(8x \u003d{-55}/{5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-55}/{40}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({8x-3}/{-9}\u003d{6}/{-6}\\)", "answer": "3/2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({8x-3}/{-9}*-9\u003d{6}/{-6}*-9\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(8x-3\u003d{-54}/{-6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(8x \u003d{-54}/{-6}+3\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(8x \u003d{-54}/{-6}+{-18}/{-6}\\)\n\\(8x \u003d{-72}/{-6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-72}/{-48}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-2x-5}/{-7}\u003d{1}/{3}\\)", "answer": "-4/3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-2x-5}/{-7}*-7\u003d{1}/{3}*-7\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-2x-5\u003d{-7}/{3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-2x \u003d{-7}/{3}+5\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-2x \u003d{-7}/{3}+{15}/{3}\\)\n\\(-2x \u003d{8}/{3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{8}/{-6}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({5x-4}/{8}\u003d{8}/{3}\\)", "answer": "76/15", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({5x-4}/{8}*8\u003d{8}/{3}*8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(5x-4\u003d{64}/{3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(5x \u003d{64}/{3}+4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(5x \u003d{64}/{3}+{12}/{3}\\)\n\\(5x \u003d{76}/{3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{76}/{15}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({4x-2}/{-4}\u003d{8}/{-8}\\)", "answer": "3/2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({4x-2}/{-4}*-4\u003d{8}/{-8}*-4\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(4x-2\u003d{-32}/{-8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(4x \u003d{-32}/{-8}+2\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(4x \u003d{-32}/{-8}+{-16}/{-8}\\)\n\\(4x \u003d{-48}/{-8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-48}/{-32}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-3x-3}/{8}\u003d{4}/{2}\\)", "answer": "-19/3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-3x-3}/{8}*8\u003d{4}/{2}*8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-3x-3\u003d{32}/{2}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-3x \u003d{32}/{2}+3\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-3x \u003d{32}/{2}+{6}/{2}\\)\n\\(-3x \u003d{38}/{2}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{38}/{-6}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({4x+4}/{3}\u003d{-8}/{-8}\\)", "answer": "-1/4", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({4x+4}/{3}*3\u003d{-8}/{-8}*3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(4x+4\u003d{-24}/{-8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(4x \u003d{-24}/{-8}-4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(4x \u003d{-24}/{-8}+{32}/{-8}\\)\n\\(4x \u003d{8}/{-8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{8}/{-32}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-6x-6}/{-4}\u003d{8}/{2}\\)", "answer": "5/3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-6x-6}/{-4}*-4\u003d{8}/{2}*-4\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-6x-6\u003d{-32}/{2}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-6x \u003d{-32}/{2}+6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-6x \u003d{-32}/{2}+{12}/{2}\\)\n\\(-6x \u003d{-20}/{2}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-20}/{-12}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-2x+8}/{8}\u003d{8}/{-5}\\)", "answer": "52/5", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-2x+8}/{8}*8\u003d{8}/{-5}*8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-2x+8\u003d{64}/{-5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-2x \u003d{64}/{-5}-8\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-2x \u003d{64}/{-5}+{40}/{-5}\\)\n\\(-2x \u003d{104}/{-5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{104}/{10}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({10x-10}/{-10}\u003d{-2}/{-3}\\)", "answer": "1/3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({10x-10}/{-10}*-10\u003d{-2}/{-3}*-10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(10x-10\u003d{20}/{-3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(10x \u003d{20}/{-3}+10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(10x \u003d{20}/{-3}+{-30}/{-3}\\)\n\\(10x \u003d{-10}/{-3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-10}/{-30}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({3x-1}/{-9}\u003d{-2}/{-8}\\)", "answer": "-5/12", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({3x-1}/{-9}*-9\u003d{-2}/{-8}*-9\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(3x-1\u003d{18}/{-8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(3x \u003d{18}/{-8}+1\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(3x \u003d{18}/{-8}+{-8}/{-8}\\)\n\\(3x \u003d{10}/{-8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{10}/{-24}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-7x+1}/{4}\u003d{-6}/{-6}\\)", "answer": "-3/7", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-7x+1}/{4}*4\u003d{-6}/{-6}*4\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-7x+1\u003d{-24}/{-6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-7x \u003d{-24}/{-6}-1\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-7x \u003d{-24}/{-6}+{6}/{-6}\\)\n\\(-7x \u003d{-18}/{-6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-18}/{42}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({4x-5}/{-4}\u003d{-3}/{-6}\\)", "answer": "3/4", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({4x-5}/{-4}*-4\u003d{-3}/{-6}*-4\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(4x-5\u003d{12}/{-6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(4x \u003d{12}/{-6}+5\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(4x \u003d{12}/{-6}+{-30}/{-6}\\)\n\\(4x \u003d{-18}/{-6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-18}/{-24}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-8x-2}/{-10}\u003d{3}/{10}\\)", "answer": "1/8", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-8x-2}/{-10}*-10\u003d{3}/{10}*-10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-8x-2\u003d{-30}/{10}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-8x \u003d{-30}/{10}+2\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-8x \u003d{-30}/{10}+{20}/{10}\\)\n\\(-8x \u003d{-10}/{10}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-10}/{-80}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-5x+6}/{-7}\u003d{-7}/{6}\\)", "answer": "-13/30", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-5x+6}/{-7}*-7\u003d{-7}/{6}*-7\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-5x+6\u003d{49}/{6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-5x \u003d{49}/{6}-6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-5x \u003d{49}/{6}+{-36}/{6}\\)\n\\(-5x \u003d{13}/{6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{13}/{-30}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-10x+1}/{3}\u003d{9}/{-10}\\)", "answer": "37/100", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-10x+1}/{3}*3\u003d{9}/{-10}*3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-10x+1\u003d{27}/{-10}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-10x \u003d{27}/{-10}-1\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-10x \u003d{27}/{-10}+{10}/{-10}\\)\n\\(-10x \u003d{37}/{-10}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{37}/{100}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-2x+2}/{-1}\u003d{7}/{-4}\\)", "answer": "1/8", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-2x+2}/{-1}*-1\u003d{7}/{-4}*-1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-2x+2\u003d{-7}/{-4}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-2x \u003d{-7}/{-4}-2\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-2x \u003d{-7}/{-4}+{8}/{-4}\\)\n\\(-2x \u003d{1}/{-4}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{1}/{8}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-7x+6}/{2}\u003d{9}/{5}\\)", "answer": "12/35", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-7x+6}/{2}*2\u003d{9}/{5}*2\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-7x+6\u003d{18}/{5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-7x \u003d{18}/{5}-6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-7x \u003d{18}/{5}+{-30}/{5}\\)\n\\(-7x \u003d{-12}/{5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-12}/{-35}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-8x-2}/{-1}\u003d{-6}/{-3}\\)", "answer": "0", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-8x-2}/{-1}*-1\u003d{-6}/{-3}*-1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-8x-2\u003d{6}/{-3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-8x \u003d{6}/{-3}+2\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-8x \u003d{6}/{-3}+{-6}/{-3}\\)\n\\(-8x \u003d{0}/{-3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{0}/{24}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-4x-8}/{-9}\u003d{7}/{9}\\)", "answer": "-1/4", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-4x-8}/{-9}*-9\u003d{7}/{9}*-9\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-4x-8\u003d{-63}/{9}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-4x \u003d{-63}/{9}+8\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-4x \u003d{-63}/{9}+{72}/{9}\\)\n\\(-4x \u003d{9}/{9}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{9}/{-36}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({9x+10}/{8}\u003d{-1}/{2}\\)", "answer": "-14/9", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({9x+10}/{8}*8\u003d{-1}/{2}*8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(9x+10\u003d{-8}/{2}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(9x \u003d{-8}/{2}-10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(9x \u003d{-8}/{2}+{-20}/{2}\\)\n\\(9x \u003d{-28}/{2}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-28}/{18}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-4x-7}/{-7}\u003d{-4}/{-9}\\)", "answer": "-35/36", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-4x-7}/{-7}*-7\u003d{-4}/{-9}*-7\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-4x-7\u003d{28}/{-9}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-4x \u003d{28}/{-9}+7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-4x \u003d{28}/{-9}+{-63}/{-9}\\)\n\\(-4x \u003d{-35}/{-9}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-35}/{36}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({2x-2}/{6}\u003d{7}/{9}\\)", "answer": "10/3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({2x-2}/{6}*6\u003d{7}/{9}*6\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(2x-2\u003d{42}/{9}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(2x \u003d{42}/{9}+2\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(2x \u003d{42}/{9}+{18}/{9}\\)\n\\(2x \u003d{60}/{9}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{60}/{18}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-4x-6}/{-1}\u003d{-2}/{-6}\\)", "answer": "-17/12", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-4x-6}/{-1}*-1\u003d{-2}/{-6}*-1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-4x-6\u003d{2}/{-6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-4x \u003d{2}/{-6}+6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-4x \u003d{2}/{-6}+{-36}/{-6}\\)\n\\(-4x \u003d{-34}/{-6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-34}/{24}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({4x+9}/{3}\u003d{8}/{-8}\\)", "answer": "-3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({4x+9}/{3}*3\u003d{8}/{-8}*3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(4x+9\u003d{24}/{-8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(4x \u003d{24}/{-8}-9\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(4x \u003d{24}/{-8}+{72}/{-8}\\)\n\\(4x \u003d{96}/{-8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{96}/{-32}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-10x-3}/{-3}\u003d{-9}/{-3}\\)", "answer": "3/5", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-10x-3}/{-3}*-3\u003d{-9}/{-3}*-3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-10x-3\u003d{27}/{-3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-10x \u003d{27}/{-3}+3\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-10x \u003d{27}/{-3}+{-9}/{-3}\\)\n\\(-10x \u003d{18}/{-3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{18}/{30}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({5x-4}/{8}\u003d{4}/{2}\\)", "answer": "4", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({5x-4}/{8}*8\u003d{4}/{2}*8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(5x-4\u003d{32}/{2}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(5x \u003d{32}/{2}+4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(5x \u003d{32}/{2}+{8}/{2}\\)\n\\(5x \u003d{40}/{2}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{40}/{10}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-7x+4}/{-5}\u003d{-2}/{6}\\)", "answer": "1/3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-7x+4}/{-5}*-5\u003d{-2}/{6}*-5\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-7x+4\u003d{10}/{6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-7x \u003d{10}/{6}-4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-7x \u003d{10}/{6}+{-24}/{6}\\)\n\\(-7x \u003d{-14}/{6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-14}/{-42}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-6x+5}/{5}\u003d{7}/{7}\\)", "answer": "0/-1", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-6x+5}/{5}*5\u003d{7}/{7}*5\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-6x+5\u003d{35}/{7}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-6x \u003d{35}/{7}-5\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-6x \u003d{35}/{7}+{-35}/{7}\\)\n\\(-6x \u003d{0}/{7}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{0}/{-42}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({2x+8}/{10}\u003d{7}/{-10}\\)", "answer": "-15/2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({2x+8}/{10}*10\u003d{7}/{-10}*10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(2x+8\u003d{70}/{-10}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(2x \u003d{70}/{-10}-8\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(2x \u003d{70}/{-10}+{80}/{-10}\\)\n\\(2x \u003d{150}/{-10}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{150}/{-20}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-9x-8}/{5}\u003d{8}/{2}\\)", "answer": "-28/9", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-9x-8}/{5}*5\u003d{8}/{2}*5\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-9x-8\u003d{40}/{2}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-9x \u003d{40}/{2}+8\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-9x \u003d{40}/{2}+{16}/{2}\\)\n\\(-9x \u003d{56}/{2}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{56}/{-18}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({4x-10}/{8}\u003d{-1}/{6}\\)", "answer": "13/6", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({4x-10}/{8}*8\u003d{-1}/{6}*8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(4x-10\u003d{-8}/{6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(4x \u003d{-8}/{6}+10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(4x \u003d{-8}/{6}+{60}/{6}\\)\n\\(4x \u003d{52}/{6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{52}/{24}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-4x-4}/{9}\u003d{-5}/{1}\\)", "answer": "41/4", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-4x-4}/{9}*9\u003d{-5}/{1}*9\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-4x-4\u003d{-45}/{1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-4x \u003d{-45}/{1}+4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-4x \u003d{-45}/{1}+{4}/{1}\\)\n\\(-4x \u003d{-41}/{1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-41}/{-4}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-6x-4}/{2}\u003d{-5}/{8}\\)", "answer": "-11/24", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-6x-4}/{2}*2\u003d{-5}/{8}*2\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-6x-4\u003d{-10}/{8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-6x \u003d{-10}/{8}+4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-6x \u003d{-10}/{8}+{32}/{8}\\)\n\\(-6x \u003d{22}/{8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{22}/{-48}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-10x+2}/{-9}\u003d{-4}/{10}\\)", "answer": "-4/25", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-10x+2}/{-9}*-9\u003d{-4}/{10}*-9\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-10x+2\u003d{36}/{10}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-10x \u003d{36}/{10}-2\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-10x \u003d{36}/{10}+{-20}/{10}\\)\n\\(-10x \u003d{16}/{10}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{16}/{-100}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-10x-10}/{6}\u003d{1}/{-10}\\)", "answer": "-47/50", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-10x-10}/{6}*6\u003d{1}/{-10}*6\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-10x-10\u003d{6}/{-10}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-10x \u003d{6}/{-10}+10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-10x \u003d{6}/{-10}+{-100}/{-10}\\)\n\\(-10x \u003d{-94}/{-10}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-94}/{100}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-7x+10}/{-2}\u003d{2}/{-9}\\)", "answer": "86/63", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-7x+10}/{-2}*-2\u003d{2}/{-9}*-2\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-7x+10\u003d{-4}/{-9}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-7x \u003d{-4}/{-9}-10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-7x \u003d{-4}/{-9}+{90}/{-9}\\)\n\\(-7x \u003d{86}/{-9}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{86}/{63}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({8x-4}/{1}\u003d{-7}/{10}\\)", "answer": "33/80", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({8x-4}/{1}*1\u003d{-7}/{10}*1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(8x-4\u003d{-7}/{10}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(8x \u003d{-7}/{10}+4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(8x \u003d{-7}/{10}+{40}/{10}\\)\n\\(8x \u003d{33}/{10}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{33}/{80}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-8x+7}/{7}\u003d{-1}/{4}\\)", "answer": "35/32", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-8x+7}/{7}*7\u003d{-1}/{4}*7\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-8x+7\u003d{-7}/{4}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-8x \u003d{-7}/{4}-7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-8x \u003d{-7}/{4}+{-28}/{4}\\)\n\\(-8x \u003d{-35}/{4}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-35}/{-32}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({7x+4}/{8}\u003d{5}/{-4}\\)", "answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({7x+4}/{8}*8\u003d{5}/{-4}*8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(7x+4\u003d{40}/{-4}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(7x \u003d{40}/{-4}-4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(7x \u003d{40}/{-4}+{16}/{-4}\\)\n\\(7x \u003d{56}/{-4}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{56}/{-28}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-8x-8}/{-10}\u003d{10}/{8}\\)", "answer": "9/16", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-8x-8}/{-10}*-10\u003d{10}/{8}*-10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-8x-8\u003d{-100}/{8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-8x \u003d{-100}/{8}+8\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-8x \u003d{-100}/{8}+{64}/{8}\\)\n\\(-8x \u003d{-36}/{8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-36}/{-64}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({5x-3}/{7}\u003d{-5}/{-3}\\)", "answer": "44/15", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({5x-3}/{7}*7\u003d{-5}/{-3}*7\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(5x-3\u003d{-35}/{-3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(5x \u003d{-35}/{-3}+3\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(5x \u003d{-35}/{-3}+{-9}/{-3}\\)\n\\(5x \u003d{-44}/{-3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-44}/{-15}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-2x+8}/{-7}\u003d{-10}/{-1}\\)", "answer": "39", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-2x+8}/{-7}*-7\u003d{-10}/{-1}*-7\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-2x+8\u003d{70}/{-1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-2x \u003d{70}/{-1}-8\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-2x \u003d{70}/{-1}+{8}/{-1}\\)\n\\(-2x \u003d{78}/{-1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{78}/{2}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({10x+7}/{-10}\u003d{7}/{-8}\\)", "answer": "7/40", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({10x+7}/{-10}*-10\u003d{7}/{-8}*-10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(10x+7\u003d{-70}/{-8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(10x \u003d{-70}/{-8}-7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(10x \u003d{-70}/{-8}+{56}/{-8}\\)\n\\(10x \u003d{-14}/{-8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-14}/{-80}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-10x-7}/{3}\u003d{7}/{-1}\\)", "answer": "7/5", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-10x-7}/{3}*3\u003d{7}/{-1}*3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-10x-7\u003d{21}/{-1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-10x \u003d{21}/{-1}+7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-10x \u003d{21}/{-1}+{-7}/{-1}\\)\n\\(-10x \u003d{14}/{-1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{14}/{10}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({10x+6}/{3}\u003d{-4}/{-4}\\)", "answer": "-3/10", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({10x+6}/{3}*3\u003d{-4}/{-4}*3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(10x+6\u003d{-12}/{-4}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(10x \u003d{-12}/{-4}-6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(10x \u003d{-12}/{-4}+{24}/{-4}\\)\n\\(10x \u003d{12}/{-4}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{12}/{-40}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-6x-3}/{-2}\u003d{9}/{1}\\)", "answer": "5/2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-6x-3}/{-2}*-2\u003d{9}/{1}*-2\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-6x-3\u003d{-18}/{1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-6x \u003d{-18}/{1}+3\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-6x \u003d{-18}/{1}+{3}/{1}\\)\n\\(-6x \u003d{-15}/{1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-15}/{-6}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({2x+1}/{2}\u003d{4}/{-5}\\)", "answer": "-13/10", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({2x+1}/{2}*2\u003d{4}/{-5}*2\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(2x+1\u003d{8}/{-5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(2x \u003d{8}/{-5}-1\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(2x \u003d{8}/{-5}+{5}/{-5}\\)\n\\(2x \u003d{13}/{-5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{13}/{-10}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-4x-4}/{-6}\u003d{-3}/{-1}\\)", "answer": "7/2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-4x-4}/{-6}*-6\u003d{-3}/{-1}*-6\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-4x-4\u003d{18}/{-1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-4x \u003d{18}/{-1}+4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-4x \u003d{18}/{-1}+{-4}/{-1}\\)\n\\(-4x \u003d{14}/{-1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{14}/{4}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({3x+1}/{5}\u003d{-5}/{5}\\)", "answer": "-2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({3x+1}/{5}*5\u003d{-5}/{5}*5\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(3x+1\u003d{-25}/{5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(3x \u003d{-25}/{5}-1\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(3x \u003d{-25}/{5}+{-5}/{5}\\)\n\\(3x \u003d{-30}/{5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-30}/{15}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({2x-4}/{10}\u003d{-4}/{6}\\)", "answer": "-4/3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({2x-4}/{10}*10\u003d{-4}/{6}*10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(2x-4\u003d{-40}/{6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(2x \u003d{-40}/{6}+4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(2x \u003d{-40}/{6}+{24}/{6}\\)\n\\(2x \u003d{-16}/{6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-16}/{12}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({6x+3}/{4}\u003d{-8}/{-3}\\)", "answer": "23/18", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({6x+3}/{4}*4\u003d{-8}/{-3}*4\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(6x+3\u003d{-32}/{-3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(6x \u003d{-32}/{-3}-3\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(6x \u003d{-32}/{-3}+{9}/{-3}\\)\n\\(6x \u003d{-23}/{-3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-23}/{-18}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-4x+7}/{-4}\u003d{9}/{8}\\)", "answer": "23/8", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-4x+7}/{-4}*-4\u003d{9}/{8}*-4\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-4x+7\u003d{-36}/{8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-4x \u003d{-36}/{8}-7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-4x \u003d{-36}/{8}+{-56}/{8}\\)\n\\(-4x \u003d{-92}/{8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-92}/{-32}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({8x-4}/{1}\u003d{2}/{-5}\\)", "answer": "9/20", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({8x-4}/{1}*1\u003d{2}/{-5}*1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(8x-4\u003d{2}/{-5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(8x \u003d{2}/{-5}+4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(8x \u003d{2}/{-5}+{-20}/{-5}\\)\n\\(8x \u003d{-18}/{-5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-18}/{-40}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-8x-6}/{-10}\u003d{-9}/{-4}\\)", "answer": "33/16", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-8x-6}/{-10}*-10\u003d{-9}/{-4}*-10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-8x-6\u003d{90}/{-4}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-8x \u003d{90}/{-4}+6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-8x \u003d{90}/{-4}+{-24}/{-4}\\)\n\\(-8x \u003d{66}/{-4}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{66}/{32}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({7x-4}/{2}\u003d{-9}/{5}\\)", "answer": "2/35", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({7x-4}/{2}*2\u003d{-9}/{5}*2\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(7x-4\u003d{-18}/{5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(7x \u003d{-18}/{5}+4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(7x \u003d{-18}/{5}+{20}/{5}\\)\n\\(7x \u003d{2}/{5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{2}/{35}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-5x-10}/{-1}\u003d{-6}/{-10}\\)", "answer": "-47/25", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-5x-10}/{-1}*-1\u003d{-6}/{-10}*-1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-5x-10\u003d{6}/{-10}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-5x \u003d{6}/{-10}+10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-5x \u003d{6}/{-10}+{-100}/{-10}\\)\n\\(-5x \u003d{-94}/{-10}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-94}/{50}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-7x+5}/{-5}\u003d{3}/{6}\\)", "answer": "15/14", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-7x+5}/{-5}*-5\u003d{3}/{6}*-5\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-7x+5\u003d{-15}/{6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-7x \u003d{-15}/{6}-5\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-7x \u003d{-15}/{6}+{-30}/{6}\\)\n\\(-7x \u003d{-45}/{6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-45}/{-42}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({2x+4}/{7}\u003d{-7}/{-4}\\)", "answer": "33/8", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({2x+4}/{7}*7\u003d{-7}/{-4}*7\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(2x+4\u003d{-49}/{-4}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(2x \u003d{-49}/{-4}-4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(2x \u003d{-49}/{-4}+{16}/{-4}\\)\n\\(2x \u003d{-33}/{-4}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-33}/{-8}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({10x-5}/{-5}\u003d{-10}/{1}\\)", "answer": "11/2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({10x-5}/{-5}*-5\u003d{-10}/{1}*-5\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(10x-5\u003d{50}/{1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(10x \u003d{50}/{1}+5\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(10x \u003d{50}/{1}+{5}/{1}\\)\n\\(10x \u003d{55}/{1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{55}/{10}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({4x+10}/{6}\u003d{7}/{5}\\)", "answer": "-2/5", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({4x+10}/{6}*6\u003d{7}/{5}*6\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(4x+10\u003d{42}/{5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(4x \u003d{42}/{5}-10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(4x \u003d{42}/{5}+{-50}/{5}\\)\n\\(4x \u003d{-8}/{5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-8}/{20}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-9x-10}/{-9}\u003d{-9}/{-2}\\)", "answer": "61/18", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-9x-10}/{-9}*-9\u003d{-9}/{-2}*-9\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-9x-10\u003d{81}/{-2}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-9x \u003d{81}/{-2}+10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-9x \u003d{81}/{-2}+{-20}/{-2}\\)\n\\(-9x \u003d{61}/{-2}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{61}/{18}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({3x+6}/{10}\u003d{9}/{1}\\)", "answer": "28", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({3x+6}/{10}*10\u003d{9}/{1}*10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(3x+6\u003d{90}/{1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(3x \u003d{90}/{1}-6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(3x \u003d{90}/{1}+{-6}/{1}\\)\n\\(3x \u003d{84}/{1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{84}/{3}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-3x+6}/{5}\u003d{-2}/{6}\\)", "answer": "23/9", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-3x+6}/{5}*5\u003d{-2}/{6}*5\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-3x+6\u003d{-10}/{6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-3x \u003d{-10}/{6}-6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-3x \u003d{-10}/{6}+{-36}/{6}\\)\n\\(-3x \u003d{-46}/{6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-46}/{-18}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-5x-6}/{-4}\u003d{3}/{1}\\)", "answer": "6/5", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-5x-6}/{-4}*-4\u003d{3}/{1}*-4\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-5x-6\u003d{-12}/{1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-5x \u003d{-12}/{1}+6\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-5x \u003d{-12}/{1}+{6}/{1}\\)\n\\(-5x \u003d{-6}/{1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-6}/{-5}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({5x+9}/{1}\u003d{-4}/{-1}\\)", "answer": "-1", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({5x+9}/{1}*1\u003d{-4}/{-1}*1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(5x+9\u003d{-4}/{-1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(5x \u003d{-4}/{-1}-9\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(5x \u003d{-4}/{-1}+{9}/{-1}\\)\n\\(5x \u003d{5}/{-1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{5}/{-5}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-4x-7}/{-8}\u003d{-5}/{-5}\\)", "answer": "1/4", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-4x-7}/{-8}*-8\u003d{-5}/{-5}*-8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-4x-7\u003d{40}/{-5}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-4x \u003d{40}/{-5}+7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-4x \u003d{40}/{-5}+{-35}/{-5}\\)\n\\(-4x \u003d{5}/{-5}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{5}/{20}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({8x+7}/{4}\u003d{3}/{4}\\)", "answer": "-1/2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({8x+7}/{4}*4\u003d{3}/{4}*4\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(8x+7\u003d{12}/{4}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(8x \u003d{12}/{4}-7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(8x \u003d{12}/{4}+{-28}/{4}\\)\n\\(8x \u003d{-16}/{4}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-16}/{32}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-9x+4}/{1}\u003d{-8}/{-8}\\)", "answer": "1/3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-9x+4}/{1}*1\u003d{-8}/{-8}*1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-9x+4\u003d{-8}/{-8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-9x \u003d{-8}/{-8}-4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-9x \u003d{-8}/{-8}+{32}/{-8}\\)\n\\(-9x \u003d{24}/{-8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{24}/{72}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-10x-7}/{-10}\u003d{-10}/{-1}\\)", "answer": "93/10", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-10x-7}/{-10}*-10\u003d{-10}/{-1}*-10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-10x-7\u003d{100}/{-1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-10x \u003d{100}/{-1}+7\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-10x \u003d{100}/{-1}+{-7}/{-1}\\)\n\\(-10x \u003d{93}/{-1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{93}/{10}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({5x-5}/{-10}\u003d{-10}/{-8}\\)", "answer": "-3/2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({5x-5}/{-10}*-10\u003d{-10}/{-8}*-10\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(5x-5\u003d{100}/{-8}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(5x \u003d{100}/{-8}+5\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(5x \u003d{100}/{-8}+{-40}/{-8}\\)\n\\(5x \u003d{60}/{-8}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{60}/{-40}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({10x-8}/{1}\u003d{-7}/{-1}\\)", "answer": "3/2", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({10x-8}/{1}*1\u003d{-7}/{-1}*1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(10x-8\u003d{-7}/{-1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(10x \u003d{-7}/{-1}+8\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(10x \u003d{-7}/{-1}+{-8}/{-1}\\)\n\\(10x \u003d{-15}/{-1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-15}/{-10}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-6x+10}/{-8}\u003d{-9}/{4}\\)", "answer": "-4/3", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-6x+10}/{-8}*-8\u003d{-9}/{4}*-8\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-6x+10\u003d{72}/{4}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-6x \u003d{72}/{4}-10\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-6x \u003d{72}/{4}+{-40}/{4}\\)\n\\(-6x \u003d{32}/{4}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{32}/{-24}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({10x-4}/{-7}\u003d{-10}/{-1}\\)", "answer": "-33/5", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({10x-4}/{-7}*-7\u003d{-10}/{-1}*-7\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(10x-4\u003d{70}/{-1}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(10x \u003d{70}/{-1}+4\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(10x \u003d{70}/{-1}+{-4}/{-1}\\)\n\\(10x \u003d{66}/{-1}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{66}/{-10}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-10x+5}/{9}\u003d{-5}/{10}\\)", "answer": "19/20", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-10x+5}/{9}*9\u003d{-5}/{10}*9\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-10x+5\u003d{-45}/{10}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-10x \u003d{-45}/{10}-5\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-10x \u003d{-45}/{10}+{-50}/{10}\\)\n\\(-10x \u003d{-95}/{10}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-95}/{-100}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({5x-8}/{3}\u003d{-10}/{6}\\)", "answer": "3/5", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({5x-8}/{3}*3\u003d{-10}/{6}*3\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(5x-8\u003d{-30}/{6}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(5x \u003d{-30}/{6}+8\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(5x \u003d{-30}/{6}+{48}/{6}\\)\n\\(5x \u003d{18}/{6}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{18}/{30}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "},
  {"type": "jqmath", "question": "Solve for x: \n\\({-3x-3}/{1}\u003d{-10}/{3}\\)", "answer": "1/9", "explanation": "Multiply by left denominator on each side:\n\\({-3x-3}/{1}*1\u003d{-10}/{3}*1\\)\n\nSimplify:\n\\(-3x-3\u003d{-10}/{3}\\)\n\nIsolate the variable:\n\\(-3x \u003d{-10}/{3}+3\\)\n\nCombine into common denominator:\n\\(-3x \u003d{-10}/{3}+{9}/{3}\\)\n\\(-3x \u003d{-1}/{3}\\)\n\nDivide by the coefficient of x on both sides:\n\\(x \u003d{-1}/{-9}\\)\n\nReduce to lowest terms: ", "prompt": "x \u003d "}
]}